https://www.cimarrontechnology.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Email
(208) 830-3750
My Account
Search for:
Privacy Policy
We welcome you to the Cimarron Technology, Inc. website. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.cimarrontechnology.com which is owned and operated by Cimarron Technology, Inc. and governs our usage of information we collect on this website. For the purposes of this statement, unless otherwise noted, all references to Cimarron Technology, Inc. include www.cimarrontechnology.com. This website is an ecommerce site. As such, its primary purpose is the collection of information for the sale and conveyance of products and services to customers. Protecting your private information that you transmit to us in your use of this website is our priority. By using this website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement, so please read it in its entirety.
Collection of Your Personal InformationWhen you submit a purchase or become a registered user of this website, we will collect sensitive and personally identifiable information, including:NameCompany nameShipping and billing addressesEmail addressTelephone numberFax numberCredit card payment informationWe may retain some of this information about you in a customer file. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction.We are not responsible for any information that users disclose to any third party by or through this website in reviews, message boards, or blog comments.We encourage you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from this website so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or other content on websites outside of this website.
Use and Sharing of Your Personal InformationWe collect and use your personal information to operate our website and deliver the products or services you have requested.We may also use your contact information to inform you of other products or services available from us. We may also contact you via surveys to conduct marketing research about your opinion of current products or services or of potential new products or services that may be offered.We do not sell, rent or lease any of your information to third parties.We may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to us, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.We may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within this website in order to determine which of our products or services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within this website to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular topic.We will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of ours; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of this website or the public.In the even that we are involved in a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, reorganization, sale of assets or change in our ownership, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction.
Automatically Collected InformationInformation about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by us. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of our business, to maintain the quality of our products and services, and to provide general statistics regarding use of this website.
Use of CookiesThis website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver malware to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize our pages, or register with this site or its services, a cookie helps this site to recall your specific information for subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, etc. When you return to this website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this website.
Security of Your Personal InformationWe secure your personal information, in particular your financial information, from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. When personal information, including credit card payment information, is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.Our website is equipped with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. Online orders to us must be placed from a secure browser that supports SSL encryption. Secure browsers will automatically enter the encrypted mode when you make a purchase. If you do not have access to a secure browser, or would like to place an order using another method, please contact us for further information on placing an offline order.
Children Under ThirteenWe do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. If you are a parent or guardian, please contact us if you believe information from or about your child has been wrongly collected by this website.
Opt-Out and UnsubscribeWe respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications by sending us an email at support@cimarrontechnology.com.
Changes to this StatementWe have sole discretion to update this statement from time to time to reflect changes in law or company policy. The most current version of this statement will be posted on this website and will govern our use of your information. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how we are protecting your information. By continuing to use the website after changes have become effective, you agree to be bound by the most recent statement and acknowledge that the revised statement applies to all information held by us.
Contact InformationWe welcome your questions or comments regarding this statement. You may contact us at:
(208) 830-3750
sales@cimarrontechnology.com
372 S Eagle Rd,
PMB 182
Eagle, ID 83616-5908 USA
Effective April 9, 2018.
(208) 830-3750
sales@cimarrontechnology.com
8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m. MST
372 S Eagle Rd,
